Marius Cristian Stan



linkedin.com/in/cristianstandev



stan.marius.cristian@gmail.com

Summary

I started working as a web developer, after a few years of managing a car rental business.

I keep in touch with the latest technologies, constantly improving my skills and learning new things.

In the past i worked as a web developer for many companies, as managing my business offered me a flexible schedule that allowed me to work subsequently as a w.d.

Experience



Frontend Web Developer

Igloo

Nov 2019 - Present (6 months +)

I work remotely in a small team that is responsible developing website templates, mantaining the main website and technically managing the WHMCS platform used for sales.

Skills: JavaScript, ReactJS, HTML5/CSS3, PHP / MYSQL, Wordpress, Git, Linux, Asana

R Founder

Rentador Auto

Oct 2014 - Feb 2020 (5 years 5 months)

- # Leading activities;
- # Office activities (contracts, billing, other company documents);
- # On-field activities (customer meetings, car rental delivery drop-off, driving;)
- # Fleet management full service;
- # Relations with company suppliers;
- # Marketing responsible Facebook Ads, Google Ads and many other channels, including graphical elements.
- # Developing and mantaining company website, including domain, server and email administration.

Meb Developer

nEAT office

Jan 2015 - May 2017 (2 years 5 months)

I was responsible with developing responsive and interactive web apps for the company, implementing the mock-ups provided by the UX/UI designers.

Skills used: JavaScript, JQuery, HTML / CSS, PHP, MySQL, Bootstrap, Wordpress.



Freelance Flash Developer

ALTFACTOR

Jan 2013 - Dec 2014 (2 years)

• Flash Developer

SIVECO Romania

May 2011 - Nov 2011 (7 months)

I was responsible developing flash educational software based on a stotyboard provided.

Motorcade Chief, driver

DEKRA

Jan 2011 - May 2011 (5 months)

Flash Developer

Softbyte Solutions Mar 2008 - Mar 2009 (1 year 1 month)

Education

Andrei Şaguna University

Master's degree, Economics 2015 - 2017

Andrei Şaguna University

Bachelor's degree, Law 2011 - 2015

Licenses & Certifications

G Digital Marketing - Google

Skills

HTML5 • CSS3 • JavaScript • ReactJS • PHP • MySQL • GIT • Wordpress